

+90 545 572 3019 · ardasevikk@gmail.com

Yenişehir Mahallesi / Ekin Sokak / Palmek Sitesi / B Blok / Daire 4 - İstanbul / Pendik

### **COMPUTER ENGINEERING**

Born on October 3, 2000 in Izmir, I completed my 4th year in Computer Engineering at Mersin University. I am interested in mobile application development, robotics development, artificial intelligence and machine learning. Thanks to the internships I completed and my school, I worked in a company where I undertook both Front-End and Back-End tasks. I have been involved in many projects. I am more in the foreground in the Front-End part, in the Back-End for now with FireBase I am improving myself. I have B2 Intermediate level English. I have an A2 driver's license.

#### **KEY COMPETENCIES**

Flutter / Dart Artificial Intelligence Python
Robotics / IOT Machine Learning .NET

Electronics FireBase Data Mining

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Artı ve Artı Teknoloji Hizmetleri San. ve Tic. A.Ş Intern Computer Engineer - Cyber Security Department

July 2024 - August 2024

I was asked to develop a cyber security training/assistance application. I was asked to provide Authentications kept with FireBase Authentication, photos kept secure with FireStore and Storage and data, slides, quizzes, rank system and artificial intelligence integration, making learning fun, but also I offered an application where they can get help from professionals on the platform at any time.

# Sim Bilişim Teknolojileri | AKINSOFT Mersin Bölge Bayi Intern Computer Engineer - ERP/CRM Development

July 2023 - August 2023

When I started my internship, it coincided with the time when the company was about to start a project. This project was to develop an ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning) application for a group of managers who had a fleet of vehicles in their company. In the application developed with Flutter, managers and employees use separate login methods, and many things such as vehicle tracking, employee tracking, income and expense tracking, location tracking, requests, etc. can be viewed with a single touch.

## Chain and Boutique Coffee Companies Barista

June 2021 - September 2023

During my student life, I worked as a barista in many chain coffee companies and boutique cafes in order to make pocket money for myself. For example, Sabiha Gökçen Airport International Department Starbucks, Sayapark Soulmate... I have a total of more than one year of experience as a barista

### **EDUCATION**

### **Computer Engineering**

Mersin University 2019- Continuing (Single Course Left)

Fen Bilimleri Highschool

2014-2018

### **SCHOOL PROJECTS**

**E-Commerce Site -.NET** 

Mersin University

**Machine Learning Distance Measurement -Python**Mersin University

Smart Pet Collar -ESP32 / Flutter

Mersin University

Online Order Analytics Data Mining - Python

Mersin University